(LOOΠΔ TV for Premier Greeting - [Line &amp; Up], START!
(LOOΠΔ 1/3 has arrived!)
#NowPlaying "LOOΠΔ 1/3 - 지금, 좋아해 (Love&amp;Live)"
(LOOΠΔ / yyxy also has arrived!)
(Lastly, LOOΠΔ/ ODD EYE CIRCLE and YeoJin have arrived!)
Kim Lip: Hello~
JinSoul: Long time no see~
Choerry &amp; YeoJin: Hello~
Choerry: It's been awhile!
JinSoul: Odd eye~ frog~!
YeoJin: What? Odd eye frog?
(This is the first day of LOOΠΔ Premier Greeting - [Line&amp;Up]!)
All: Hello, we're LOOΠΔ!
(It's really hard to shoot them in one frame!)
HaSeul: I guess it's the very first time to be here, in front of the camera, as a whole group.
HaSeul: You know, we've gathered here to do our first fan meeting today~!
HaSeul: We're going to do a rehearsal~
HaSeul: And we'll do our best to present great performances for you today~!
JinSoul: We can do well, right?
(All the members are so confident!)
All: Of course!
Choerry: Let's work hard!
(All the members are so confident!)
All: Fighting
JinSoul: Shall we chant the slogan? It's been a while!
HaSeul: Really? Will you really do that?
(Sure, let's go!)
(The youngest members of LOOΠΔ are reading a script, like doing a role play!)
YeoJin: Hello, I'm YeoJin, the fourth member of LOOΠΔ
Choerry: Okay, you will have to do like this!